<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on APorous Inc.</title>
    <link>https://www.aporous.github.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on APorous Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.aporous.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prototype Engineering</title>
      <link>https://www.aporous.github.io/services/prototype_engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aporous.github.io/services/prototype_engineering/</guid>
      <description>The battery industry has gone through rapid changes in the past twenty years. We support product developments in the areas of:   Separators (Lithium, Lead-Acid, Alkaline, Ceramic Coating)     Food Packaging     Membranes and Filters    Available R&amp;amp;D Equipment:   &amp;mdash;Resin dry mixers (1 to 500 kg capacity)     &amp;mdash;Twin screw extruder for compounding (high shear liquid injection and vacuum capability)     &amp;mdash;Thin Film Co-Extrusion (two twin screw 30mm extruders, 10 – 500 microns thickness)     &amp;mdash;Cast film die width to 25 cm (multi-layers AA, AB, ABA or ABC configuration layers)     &amp;mdash;Cast film lamination capability (to nonwovens)     &amp;mdash;Resin moisture dryer prior to compounding (10 to 700 kg capacity)     &amp;mdash;Longitudinal MDO stretch (1 to 20 m/min)     &amp;mdash;Transverse TDO stretch (1 to 10 m/min, 10 cm min’ inlet, 100 cm max’ output)     &amp;mdash;Laboratory biaxial stretches (4 x 4 cm)     &amp;mdash;Lab testing capability (moisture, tensile, puncture, Gurley, porosity, resistance, chemical stability, plus external resources)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toll Plastic Resin Production</title>
      <link>https://www.aporous.github.io/services/toll_plastic_resin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aporous.github.io/services/toll_plastic_resin/</guid>
      <description>APorous specializes in custom plastic compounding and master-batching, where customers have special needs in formulation and/or processing that cannot be obtained from traditional resin manufacturers. In such cases, APorous is ideally set-up for development and manufacturing of melt blends, alloys, compatible plastic compounds, filled polymers and other polymer modifications. Examples of such applications may be breathable film resin or electrolyte conductive membranes. The product may be jointly developed between the client and APorous, or using customer’s proprietary recipes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Consulting Team</title>
      <link>https://www.aporous.github.io/services/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aporous.github.io/services/consulting/</guid>
      <description>APorous performs contract product developments for multi-national clients. Our clients attribute our success to the &amp;ldquo;experiences, insights and dedication,&amp;rdquo; we follow through from development to product manufacturing. References can be furnished upon request.
 William Yen (President, 30 years of battery and separator experience, expertise in melt extrusion, lead-acid, alkaline and lithium separators and batteries, 11 patents granted, M.S. Chemical Engineering Northeastern University).
 Dr. Han Kuo (Consultant, 40 years of lithium battery manufacturing experience, prior President of Eone Moli, 25 patents granted, UCLA PhD in electrochemistry).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
